<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Resolve Cafe]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Latest News from Resolve Cafe]]></description>
        <link>https://resolve.cafe</link>
        <generator>Resolve Cafe</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:35:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://resolve.cafe/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Saturday 3rd June 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>In this video series, Igor Riđanović will be demonstrating proof-of-concept OpenAI GPT and DaVinci Resolve integrations, starting with a virtual Resolve assistant.</p>
<p>Imagine having all the information you need right at your fingertips within Resolve itself. No more switching between Facebook, Blackmagic Forum, or other platforms. Just ask your questions directly in Resolve.</p>
<p>Igor would love to hear your thoughts on this integration. Are there other GPT AI use cases you'd like to see in Resolve?</p>
<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p9wJcn8mGGs"><img src="/static/resolve-chatgpt.jpg" alt=""></a>{target=&quot;_blank&quot;}</p>
<hr>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#saturday-3rd-june-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Saturday 3rd June 2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wednesday 31st May 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Colourlab Ai</strong> is having a Spring Flash Sale! Up to 50% Off on Our Color Grading Software - Only 48 Hours Left!</p>
<p>Spring is in the air, and so are the savings!</p>
<p>Here's what's on offer:</p>
<p><strong>Colourlab Ai Studio Annual License:</strong> Get a whopping 50% off on their Colourlab Ai Studio Annual License. This brings the cost of Colourlab Ai, Look Designer Plugin, and Grainlab Plugin down to just $249. That's less than the cost of a single plugin! Considering the combined value of all three applications is over $1000, this is a massive saving. Use the code <code>springstudio50</code> to take advantage of this offer.
<strong>Look Designer Perpetual Licenses:</strong> Colourlab Ai is offering a 30% discount on their Look Designer Perpetual Licenses. This means you can own Look Designer forever for just $349. Look Designer 3.0 for Davinci and Premiere runs on both Mac and PC and is the perfect companion for creating X01 files, Look Design, Look Testing, EL Zones, and Full Color Management. Use the code <code>springlook30</code> to avail this offer.</p>
<p>Buy Colourlab Ai Studio <a href="https://colourlab.ai/colourlab-ai-studio-2-yearly/">here</a>{target=&quot;_blank&quot;}.
Buy Look Designer Perpetual <a href="https://colourlab.ai/look-designer-resolve-perpetual/">here</a>{target=&quot;_blank&quot;}</p>
<hr>
<p>{{ include &quot;sponsors/scaling-fix.md&quot; }}</p>
<hr>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#wednesday-31st-may-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Wednesday 31st May 2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tuesday 30th May 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Following on from the interest in <a href="https://fcp.cafe">FCP Cafe</a>{target=&quot;_blank&quot;}, Chris at <a href="https://latenitefilms.com/technology/">LateNite</a>{target=&quot;_blank&quot;} has thrown together this site to be a new &quot;home page&quot; and community for professional editors using DaVinCi Resolve.</p>
<p>We want this site to be:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Open:</strong> This site will remain open-source on GitHub for anyone to suggest pull requests</li>
<li><strong>Up-to-date &amp; Relevant:</strong> We want this site to always be up-to-date and relevant</li>
<li><strong>No bullshit:</strong> We want this site to be honest, truthful, useful and professional</li>
<li><strong>Community Driven:</strong> This isn't our site, it's &quot;owned&quot; by the professional DaVinci Resolve Community</li>
<li><strong>Modern:</strong> This site should work great on the latest browsers, including mobile</li>
<li><strong>Fast &amp; Clean:</strong> This site should load quickly, and be easy to navigate</li>
<li><strong>No analytics or user tracking:</strong> No cookies here!</li>
</ul>
<p>This is still very much a work-in-progress, and we'll be adding content gradually over the coming weeks and months.</p>
<hr>
<p>{{ include &quot;advertise-banner.md&quot; }}</p>
<hr>
<p>{{ include &quot;giscus.md&quot; }}</p>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#tuesday-30th-may-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Tuesday 30th May 2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>