<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Resolve Cafe]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Latest News from Resolve Cafe]]></description>
        <link>https://resolve.cafe</link>
        <generator>Resolve Cafe</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 21:53:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://resolve.cafe/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Make FCP Cafe your Home Page]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>+++ Safari</p>
<ol>
<li>In the top left corner of your screen, select <strong>Safari</strong> and then <strong>Preferences</strong> and then <strong>General</strong>.</li>
<li>Next to <strong>New windows open with</strong> and <strong>New tabs open with</strong>, select <strong>Homepage</strong>.</li>
<li>Next to <strong>Homepage</strong> enter: <code>https://fcp.cafe</code>.
+++ Chrome</li>
<li>In the top right corner of your computer's browser, click <strong>More</strong> icon and then <strong>Settings</strong>.</li>
<li>Under <strong>Appearance</strong>, turn on <strong>Show home button</strong>.</li>
<li>Select your current homepage, then, enter: <code>https://fcp.cafe</code>.
+++ Firefox</li>
<li>Drag this tab to the <strong>Home</strong> button, then release.</li>
<li>Click <strong>Yes</strong>.
+++ Microsoft Edge</li>
<li>In the upper right corner of your browser, select the <strong>More</strong> icon and then <strong>Settings</strong>.</li>
<li>Under <strong>Set your homepage</strong>, click the Down arrow and then <strong>A specific page or pages</strong>.</li>
<li>If you have a current homepage: Next to the URL, click <strong>X</strong>.</li>
<li>Click <strong>Enter a URL</strong>. Then, type: <code>https://fcp.cafe</code>.
+++ Internet Explorer</li>
<li>In the menu bar on the top of your browser, click <strong>Tools</strong>.</li>
<li>Select <strong>Internet Options</strong>.</li>
<li>Click the <strong>General</strong> tab.</li>
<li>Under &quot;Home page,&quot; enter: <code>https://fcp.cafe</code>.</li>
<li>Click OK.</li>
<li>Restart your browser.
+++</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<hr>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#make-fcp-cafe-your-home-page</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Make FCP Cafe your Home Page</guid>
            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wednesday 31st May 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Colourlab Ai</strong> is having a Spring Flash Sale! Up to 50% Off on Our Color Grading Software - Only 48 Hours Left!</p>
<p>Spring is in the air, and so are the savings!</p>
<p>Here's what's on offer:</p>
<p><strong>Colourlab Ai Studio Annual License:</strong> Get a whopping 50% off on their Colourlab Ai Studio Annual License. This brings the cost of Colourlab Ai, Look Designer Plugin, and Grainlab Plugin down to just $249. That's less than the cost of a single plugin! Considering the combined value of all three applications is over $1000, this is a massive saving. Use the code <code>springstudio50</code> to take advantage of this offer.
<strong>Look Designer Perpetual Licenses:</strong> Colourlab Ai is offering a 30% discount on their Look Designer Perpetual Licenses. This means you can own Look Designer forever for just $349. Look Designer 3.0 for Davinci and Premiere runs on both Mac and PC and is the perfect companion for creating X01 files, Look Design, Look Testing, EL Zones, and Full Color Management. Use the code <code>springlook30</code> to avail this offer.</p>
<p>Buy Colourlab Ai Studio <a href="https://colourlab.ai/colourlab-ai-studio-2-yearly/">here</a>.
Buy Look Designer Perpetual <a href="https://colourlab.ai/look-designer-resolve-perpetual/">here</a></p>
<hr>
<p>info Sponsored
<strong>DaVinci Resolve Studio Scaling Fix:</strong> Fix Scaling issues in DaVinci Resolve Studio for FCPX and Premiere sequences imported via XML and FCPXML. <a href="https://julien.chichignoud.com/resolve-script-scaling-fix">Download Now!</a></p>
<hr>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#wednesday-31st-may-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Wednesday 31st May 2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tuesday 30th May 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Following on from the interest in <a href="https://fcp.cafe">FCP Cafe</a>, Chris at <a href="https://latenitefilms.com/technology/">LateNite</a> has thrown together this site to be a new &quot;home page&quot; and community for professional editors using DaVinCi Resolve.</p>
<p>We want this site to be:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Open:</strong> This site will remain open-source on GitHub for anyone to suggest pull requests</li>
<li><strong>Up-to-date &amp; Relevant:</strong> We want this site to always be up-to-date and relevant</li>
<li><strong>No bullshit:</strong> We want this site to be honest, truthful, useful and professional</li>
<li><strong>Community Driven:</strong> This isn't our site, it's &quot;owned&quot; by the professional DaVinci Resolve Community</li>
<li><strong>Modern:</strong> This site should work great on the latest browsers, including mobile</li>
<li><strong>Fast &amp; Clean:</strong> This site should load quickly, and be easy to navigate</li>
<li><strong>No analytics or user tracking:</strong> No cookies here!</li>
</ul>
<p>This is still very much a work-in-progress, and we'll be adding content gradually over the coming weeks and months.</p>
<hr>
<hr>
<p>{{ include &quot;giscus.md&quot; }}</p>
]]></description>
            <link>https://resolve.cafe/#tuesday-30th-may-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">Tuesday 30th May 2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>